A Guide to the Foundation Center of New York records FA023
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Program and Project Files, 1924-1999; 2
  - Programs, 1924-1998; 1
    - Foundation Correspondence, 1924-1979; C
      - United States - New York - New York Community Trust, 1945-1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
        Unidentified, Male, (2 x 2.5)", black and white Unidentified, Family, 2 images (3.5 x 3.5)", black and white
        See also Reel 98, Frame 0991.
      - United States - Alabama, 1945-1966 (Reel 92, Frame 805)
      - United States - Alaska, 1960 (Reel 92, Frame 824)
      - United States - Arizona, 1966-1969 (Reel 92, Frame 826)
      - United States - Arkansas, 1952-1975 (Reel 92, Frame 834)
      - United States - California, 1924-1970 (Reel 92, Frame 840)
      - United States - California - The Asia Foundation, 1968-1971 (Reel 92, Frame 1,249)
      - United States - California - The Claremore Fund, 1956-1962 (Reel 93, Frame 1)
      - United States - California - The Grantsmanship Center, 1973 (Reel 93, Frame 116)
      - United States - California - Howland Project, 1964-1966 (Reel 93, Frame 119)
      - United States - California - The James Irvine Foundation, 1965-1969 (Reel 93, Frame 143)
      - United States - California - Rosenberg Foundation, 1945-1969 (Reel 93, Frame 186)
      - United States - California - San Francisco Foundation, 1949-1970 (Reel 93, Frame 334)
      - United States - Colorado, 1930-1971 (Reel 93, Frame 474)
      - United States - Colorado - El Pomar Foundation, 1951-1968 (Reel 93, Frame 540)
      - United States - Connecticut, 1930-1971 (Reel 93, Frame 574)
      - United States - Connecticut - Hartford Foundation for Public Giving, 1949-1979 (Reel 93, Frame 772)
      - United States - Connecticut - Edward W. Hazen Foundation, 1949-1969 (Reel 93, Frame 832)
      - United States - Connecticut - The New Haven Foundation, 1949-1973 (Reel 93, Frame 869)
      - United States - Delaware, 1945-1971 (Reel 93, Frame 1,174)
      - United States - Delaware - The Nemours Foundation, 1951-1969 (Reel 93, Frame 1,221)
      - United States - Florida, 1945-1971 (Reel 93, Frame 1,256)
      - United States - Georgia, 1928-1970 (Reel 94, Frame 1)
      - United States - Georgia - Metropolitan Foundation of Atlanta, 1960-1965 (Reel 94, Frame 88)
      - United States - Georgia - Southern Education Foundation, 1954-1970 (Reel 94, Frame 126)
      - United States - Hawaii, 1957-1969 (Reel 94, Frame 210)
      - United States - Hawaii - Watumull Foundation, 1945-1969 (Reel 94, Frame 238)
      - United States - Idaho, 1930-1953 (Reel 94, Frame 288)
      - United States - Illinois, 1939-1970 (Reel 94, Frame 292)
      - United States - Illinois - American Bar Foundation, 1957-1967 (Reel 94, Frame 414)
      - United States - Illinois - Chicago - Miscellaneous (A-K), 1947-1970 (Reel 94, Frame 456)
      - United States - Illinois - Chicago - Miscellaneous (L-Z), 1929-1969 (Reel 94, Frame 701)
      - United States - Illinois - Chicago Community Trust, 1950-1970 (Reel 94, Frame 856)
      - United States - Illinois - Community Fund of Chicago, 1949-1953 (Reel 94, Frame 915)
      - United States - Illinois - David C. Cook Foundation, 1953-1968 (Reel 94, Frame 933)
      - United States - Illinois - Edison Electric Institute, 1963-1964 (Reel 94, Frame 1,037)
      - United States - Illinois - Field Foundation, 1956-1967 (Reel 94, Frame 1,063)
      - United States - Illinois - Inland Steel-Ryerson Foundation, Inc., 1951-1968 (Reel 94, Frame 1,077)
      - United States - Illinois - International Harvester Foundation, 1951-1968 (Reel 94, Frame 1,120)
      - United States - Illinois - National Committee on Foundations and Trusts for Community Welfare, 1953 (Reel 94, Frame 1,138)
      - United States - Illinois - National Society for Crippled Children and Adults, 1949-1959 (Reel 94, Frame 1,149)
      - United States - Illinois - Rotary Educational Foundation, 1945-1958 (Reel 94, Frame 1,193)
      - United States - Illinois - Sears-Roebuck Foundation, 1951-1970 (Reel 94, Frame 1,209)
      - United States - Illinois - Wieboldt Foundation, 1961-1967 (Reel 94, Frame 1,256)
      - United States - Illinois - Woods Charitable Fund, Inc., 1951-1967 (Reel 94, Frame 1,285)
      - United States - Indiana, 1945-1969 (Reel 95, Frame 1)
      - United States - Indiana - The Indianapolis Foundation, 1951-1968 (Reel 95, Frame 130)
      - United States - Indiana - Lilly Endowment, Inc., 1950-1970 (Reel 95, Frame 153)
      - United States - Iowa, 1926-1970 (Reel 95, Frame 313)
        See Box 1, Folder 4, for photographs.
      - United States - Kansas, 1927-1970 (Reel 95, Frame 350)
      - United States - Kentucky, 1926-1970 (Reel 95, Frame 408)
      - United States - Louisiana, 1952-1963 (Reel 95, Frame 428)
      - United States - Louisiana - Edward G. Schlieder Education Foundation, 1954-1970 (Reel 95, Frame 436)
      - United States - Maine, 1960 (Reel 95, Frame 482)
      - United States - Maryland, 1945-1973 (Reel 95, Frame 486)
      - United States - Massachusetts, 1926-1975 (Reel 95, Frame 513)
      - United States - Massachusetts - The Associated Foundation of Greater Boston, 1969-1971 (Reel 95, Frame 848)
      - United States - Massachusetts - Committee of the Permanent Charity Fund, Inc., 1953-1969 (Reel 95, Frame 882)
      - United States - Massachusetts - The Franklin Foundation, 1917-1962 (Reel 95, Frame 949)
      - United States - Massachusetts - Godfrey M. Hyams Trust, 1945-1954 (Reel 95, Frame 996)
      - United States - Michigan, 1944-1970 (Reel 95, Frame 1,023)
      - United States - Michigan - Ford Motor Company Fund, 1945-1965 (Reel 95, Frame 1,247)
      - United States - Michigan - James Foster Foundation, 1954-1957 (Reel 96, Frame 1)
      - United States - Michigan - W. K. Kellogg Foundation, 1930-1971 (Reel 96, Frame 89)
      - United States - Michigan - The Kresge Foundation, 1945-1969 (Reel 96, Frame 293)
      - United States - Michigan - Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, 1945-1970 (Reel 96, Frame 367)
      - United States - Michigan - United Foundation, 1949-1951 (Reel 96, Frame 427)
      - United States - Minnesota, 1930-1970 (Reel 96, Frame 458)
      - United States - Minnesota - Louis W. & Maud Hill Family Foundation, 1953-1970 (Reel 96, Frame 700)
      - United States - Mississippi, 1947-1970 (Reel 96, Frame 945)
      - United States - Mississippi - Mississippi Valley Historical Association, 1957-1958 (Reel 96, Frame 951)
      - United States - Missouri, 1926-1969 (Reel 96, Frame 987)
      - United States - Missouri - Danforth Foundation, 1954-1970 (Reel 97, Frame 1)
      - United States - Missouri - Danforth Foundation - Danforth Case, 1962-1965 (Reel 97, Frame 314)
      - United States - Missouri - Danforth Foundation - Meeting on Precollegiate Education, 1969-1970 (Reel 97, Frame 401)
      - United States - Missouri - Danforth Foundation - Meeting of Religious Studies in Higher Education, 1968-1969 (Reel 97, Frame 517)
      - United States - Missouri - Danforth Foundation - Theological Education Program Proposal, 1967-1968 (Reel 97, Frame 568)
      - United States - Missouri - Kansas City Association of Trusts and Foundations, 1956-1970 (Reel 97, Frame 653)
      - United States - Montana, 1965 (Reel 97, Frame 771)
      - United States - Nebraska, 1952-1967 (Reel 97, Frame 773)
      - United States - Nevada, 1966 (Reel 97, Frame 817)
      - United States - Nevada - Max Fleischmann Foundation of Nevada, 1953-1971 (Reel 97, Frame 823)
      - United States - New Hampshire, 1945-1969 (Reel 97, Frame 903)
      - United States - New Hampshire - Register - Charitable Trusts - Ernest R. D'Amours, 1949-1962 (Reel 97, Frame 953)
      - United States - New Jersey (A-K), 1930-1970 (Reel 97, Frame 975)
      - United States - New Jersey (L-Z), 1945-1970 (Reel 98, Frame 1)
      - United States - New Jersey - Fannie E. Rippel Foundation, 1951-1970 (Reel 98, Frame 252)
      - United States - New Jersey - Victoria Foundation, Inc., 1945-1970 (Reel 98, Frame 276)
      - United States - New Jersey - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation, 1960-1970 (Reel 98, Frame 301)
      - United States - New Mexico, 1957-1975 (Reel 98, Frame 339)
      - United States - New York, 1931-1971 (Reel 98, Frame 348)
      - United States - New York - Allen Arlett, 1969-1974 (Reel 98, Frame 564)
      - United States - New York - The Conference Board, 1972 (Reel 98, Frame 664)
      - United States - New York - Coudert Brothers - George Nebolsine, 1961-1963 (Reel 98, Frame 668)
      - United States - New York - Council on Foundations, Inc., 1971-1974 (Reel 98, Frame 708)
      - United States - New York - The Ford Foundation, 1969-1974 (Reel 98, Frame 734)
      - United States - New York - General Electric Foundation, 1951-1970 (Reel 98, Frame 744)
      - United States - New York - The Rosamond Gifford Charitable Corporation, 1958-1976 (Reel 98, Frame 797)
      - United States - New York - Institute of Modern Languages, Inc., 1969-1970 (Reel 98, Frame 887)
      - United States - New York - New World Foundation, 1954-1969 (Reel 98, Frame 893)
      - United States - New York - New York Community Trust, 1945-1970 (Reel 98, Frame 991)
        See Box 1, Folder 5, for photographs.
      - United States - New York - New York Foundation, 1945-1966 (Reel 98, Frame 1,242)
      - United States - New York - The Nutrition Foundation, Inc., 1950-1966 (Reel 98, Frame 1,265)
      - United States - New York - Olin Foundation, Inc., 1947-1970 (Reel 99, Frame 1)
      - United States - New York - Gustavus and Louis Pfeiffer Research Foundation, 1945-1964 (Reel 99, Frame 162)
      - United States - New York - Phelps-Stokes Fund, 1956-1974 (Reel 99, Frame 189)
      - United States - New York - Puerto Ricans-Spanish Speaking Communities, 1972-1973 (Reel 99, Frame 236)
      - United States - New York - Research Corporation, 1945-1970 (Reel 99, Frame 243)
      - United States - New York - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Inc., 1945-1976 (Reel 99, Frame 402)
      - United States - New York - The Rockefeller Foundation, 1945-1973 (Reel 99, Frame 649)
      - United States - New York - The Rockefeller Institute, 1960 (Reel 99, Frame 1,079)
      - United States - New York - Benjamin Rosenthal Foundation, Inc., 1951-1965 (Reel 99, Frame 1,082)
      - United States - New York - Russell Sage Foundation, 1957-1971 (Reel 100, Frame 1)
      - United States - New York - Russell Sage Foundation - Project - Charitable Contributions of Wisconsin Residents, 1963-1964 (Reel 100, Frame 464)
      - United States - New York - Russell Sage Foundation - Meeting on Future Research on Foundations, September 30, 1970 (Reel 100, Frame 479)
      - United States - New York - Shell Companies Foundation, 1951-1970 (Reel 100, Frame 520)
      - United States - New York - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 1945-1971 (Reel 100, Frame 603)
      - United States - New York - Spectemur Agendo, Inc., 1965-1970 (Reel 100, Frame 818)
      - United States - New York - Twentieth Century Fund, 1945-1969 (Reel 100, Frame 872)
      - United States - New York - United Community Fund and Council, 1950-1963 (Reel 100, Frame 1,034)
      - United States - New York - United States Steel Foundation, 1951-1970 (Reel 100, Frame 1,107)
      - United States - New York - Vas Dias International, 1969 (Reel 100, Frame 1,254)
      - United States - New York - The Helen Hay Whitney Foundation, 1955-1964 (Reel 100, Frame 1,270)
      - United States - North Carolina, 1948-1970 (Reel 101, Frame 1)
      - United States - North Carolina - Mary Reynolds Babcock Foundation, Inc., 1961-1970 (Reel 101, Frame 62)
      - United States - North Carolina - The Winston-Salem Foundation, 1960-1970 (Reel 101, Frame 66)
      - United States - North Dakota, 1964 (Reel 101, Frame 97)
      - United States - Ohio, 1931-1971 (Reel 101, Frame 101)
      - United States - Ohio - The Cleveland Foundation, 1953-1970 (Reel 101, Frame 424)
      - United States - Ohio - Charles F. Kettering Foundation, 1962-1973 (Reel 101, Frame 616)
      - United States - Ohio - Charles F. Kettering Foundation - Conference on the Future of Foundations, November 11-13, 1970 (Reel 101, Frame 936)
      - United States - Ohio - Edward Drummond Libbey Estate, 1953-1957 (Reel 101, Frame 1,039)
      - United States - Ohio - The Weatherhead Foundation, 1969-1970 (Reel 101, Frame 1,067)
      - United States - Oklahoma, 1945-1970 (Reel 101, Frame 1,128)
      - United States - Oregon, 1945-1962 (Reel 101, Frame 1,162)
      - United States - Pennsylvania, 1930-1972 (Reel 102, Frame 1)
      - United States - Pennsylvania - Board of Directors of City Trusts - City of Philadelphia, 1945-1962 (Reel 102, Frame 293)
      - United States - Pennsylvania - Buhl Foundation, 1945-1969 (Reel 102, Frame 342)
      - United States - Pennsylvania - Carnegie Hero Fund Commission, 1955-1970 (Reel 102, Frame 372)
      - United States - Pennsylvania - Charitable Registration Bill - Department of Justice, 1961-1966 (Reel 102, Frame 415)
      - United States - Pennsylvania - Samuel S. Fels Fund, 1945-1969 (Reel 102, Frame 465)
      - United States - Pennsylvania - Maurice and Laura Falk Foundation, 1945-1970 (Reel 102, Frame 529)
      - United States - Pennsylvania - Independence Foundation, 1962-1970 (Reel 102, Frame 629)
      - United States - Pennsylvania - The A. W. Mellon Educational and Charitable Trust, 1945-1969 (Reel 102, Frame 651)
      - United States - Pennsylvania - Richard King Mellon Foundation, 1954-1970 (Reel 102, Frame 788)
      - United States - Pennsylvania - The Pew Memorial Trust, 1954-1969 (Reel 102, Frame 839)
      - United States - Pennsylvania - The Philadelphia Foundation, 1944-1967 (Reel 102, Frame 857)
      - United States - Pennsylvania - Pittsburgh - Miscellaneous, 1930-1966 (Reel 102, Frame 921)
      - United States - Pennsylvania - The Pittsburgh Foundation, 1945-1969 (Reel 102, Frame 994)
      - United States - Pennsylvania - Provident Tradesmens Bank and Trust Company, 1962 (Reel 102, Frame 1,128)
      - United States - Pennsylvania - Sarah Mellon Scaife Foundation, 1949-1969 (Reel 102, Frame 1,178)
      - United States - Pennsylvania - Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation, Inc., 1945-1962 (Reel 102, Frame 1,222)
      - United States - Pennsylvania - Smith Kline and Frence Foundation, 1956-1969 (Reel 102, Frame 1,251)
      - United States - Pennsylvania - Trexler Foundation, 1930-1970 (Reel 103, Frame 1)
      - United States - Rhode Island, 1945-1958 (Reel 103, Frame 84)
      - United States - Rhode Island - The Rhode Island Foundation, 1944-1968 (Reel 103, Frame 100)
      - United States - Rhode Island - Textron, Inc., 1949-1954 (Reel 103, Frame 123)
      - United States - South Carolina, 1951-1970 (Reel 103, Frame 129)
      - United States - Tennessee, 1945-1970 (Reel 103, Frame 142)
      - United States - Tennessee - Education Commission - Southern Baptist Convention, 1952 (Reel 103, Frame 181)
      - United States - Tennessee - Educational Institutions of the Methodist Church, 1951-1953 (Reel 103, Frame 207)
      - United States - Texas, 1921-1971 (Reel 103, Frame 263)
      - United States - Texas - Amarillo Area Foundation, 1959-1966 (Reel 103, Frame 480)
      - United States - Texas - Amon G. Carter Foundation, 1953-1964 (Reel 103, Frame 514)
      - United States - Texas - Conference of Southern Foundations, 1953-1969 (Reel 103, Frame 540)
      - United States - Texas - Conference of Southern Foundations - 5th-16th Annual Conference, 1953-1964 (Reel 103, Frame 601)
      - United States - Texas - Conference of Southern Foundations - 17th Annual Conference, April 22-24, 1965 (Reel 103, Frame 762)
      - United States - Texas - Conference of Southern Foundations - 18th Annual Conference, May 5-6, 1966 (Reel 103, Frame 803)
      - United States - Texas - Conference of Southern Foundations - 19th Annual Conference, April 12-14, 1967 (Reel 103, Frame 824)
      - United States - Texas - Conference of Southern Foundations - 20th Annual Conference, May 9-10, 1968 (Reel 103, Frame 853)
      - United States - Texas - Conference of Southern Foundations - 21st Annual Conference, May 8-10, 1969 (Reel 103, Frame 899)
      - United States - Texas - Conference of Southern Foundations - 22nd Annual Conference, April 8-10, 1970 (Reel 103, Frame 934)
      - United States - Texas - Cooper Foundation, 1959-1967 (Reel 103, Frame 952)
      - United States - Texas - The Hogg Foundation, 1954-1970 (Reel 103, Frame 989)
      - United States - Texas - The Hogg Foundation - Philanthropy in the Southwest, 1963-1965 (Reel 103, Frame 1,129)
      - United States - Texas - The Moody Foundation, 1955-1971 (Reel 103, Frame 1,211)
      - United States - Texas - Perot Foundation, 1969 (Reel 103, Frame 1,299)
      - United States - Texas - Minnie Stevens Piper Foundation, 1957-1966 (Reel 103, Frame 1,313)
      - United States - Texas - Robert A. Welch Foundation, 1954-1970 (Reel 104, Frame 1)
      - United States - Vermont, 1952-1972 (Reel 104, Frame 28)
      - United States - Virginia, 1945-1971 (Reel 104, Frame 35)
      - United States - Virginia - Inter-American Foundation, 1972-1973 (Reel 104, Frame 122)
      - United States - Virginia - National Association of Foundations, 1957-1971 (Reel 104, Frame 140)
      - United States - Washington, 1949-1975 (Reel 104, Frame 268)
      - United States - Washington - The Seattle Foundation, 1958-1966 (Reel 104, Frame 325)
      - United States - Washington, D. C., 1936-1974 (Reel 104, Frame 420)
      - United States - Washington, D. C. - Margot Brinkley, 1973 (Reel 104, Frame 595)
      - United States - Washington, D. C. - Carnegie Institution of Washington, 1953-1971 (Reel 104, Frame 597)
      - United States - Washington, D. C. - Pan American Development Foundation, 1963-1974 (Reel 104, Frame 640)
      - United States - Washington, D. C. - United States Department of State, 1973-1974 (Reel 104, Frame 724)
      - United States - Washington, D. C. - United States Senate, 1973 (Reel 104, Frame 751)
      - United States - West Virginia, 1928-1966 (Reel 104, Frame 807)
      - United States - Wisconsin, 1931-1974 (Reel 104, Frame 818)
      - United States - Wisconsin - Johnson Foundation, 1957-1970 (Reel 104, Frame 937)
      - United States - Wyoming, 1955-1957 (Reel 104, Frame 1,345)
      - Series 2.1C - Program and Project Files - Programs - Foundation Correspondence - Foreign Section, undated (Reel 105, Frame 1)
      - Foreign, 1961-1970 (Reel 105, Frame 2)
      - Foreign, 1969 (Reel 105, Frame 72)
      - Foreign, 1969-1970 (Reel 105, Frame 166)
      - Foreign, 1970-1971 (Reel 105, Frame 240)
      - Foreign, 1971-1972 (Reel 105, Frame 351)
      - Foreign, 1970-1974 (Reel 105, Frame 507)
      - Foreign - Africa, 1969-1970 (Reel 105, Frame 764)
      - Foreign - Argentina, 1972-1974 (Reel 105, Frame 767)
      - Foreign - Argentina - Funcacion Bariloche, 1969-1971 (Reel 105, Frame 816)
      - Foreign - Argentina - Instituto Torcuato Di Tella, 1969-1973 (Reel 105, Frame 823)
      - Foreign - Australia, 1968-1975 (Reel 105, Frame 833)
      - Foreign - Australia - Australian Directory, 1962-1974 (Reel 105, Frame 999)
      - Foreign - Australia - Australian Development Research Foundation, 1960 (Reel 105, Frame 1,046)
      - Foreign - Australia - The James N. Kirby Foundation, 1970-1974 (Reel 105, Frame 1,049)
      - Foreign - Australia - The Myer Foundation, 1967-1974 (Reel 105, Frame 1,056)
      - Foreign - Australia - The National Youth Council of Australia, 1966 (Reel 105, Frame 1,148)
      - Foreign - Australia - The Ian Potter Foundation, 1970-1974 (Reel 105, Frame 1,150)
      - Foreign - Australia - Ian Clunies Ross Memorial Foundation, 1966 (Reel 105, Frame 1,164)
      - Foreign - Australia - The Peter Stuyvesant Trust for the Development of the Arts, 1969-1970 (Reel 105, Frame 1,169)
      - Foreign - Australia - Tyree Foundation, 1970-1971 (Reel 105, Frame 1,173)
      - Foreign - Australia - The Winston Churchill Memorial Trust, 1970-1972 (Reel 105, Frame 1,177)
      - Foreign - Austria, 1972 (Reel 105, Frame 1,185)
      - Foreign - Belgium, 1969-1973 (Reel 105, Frame 1,189)
      - Foreign - Belgium - Fondation Universitaire, 1970 (Reel 105, Frame 1,195)
      - Foreign - Belgium - Fonds National de la Recherche Scientifique, 1970-1972 (Reel 105, Frame 1,198)
      - Foreign - Canada, 1957-1974 (Reel 105, Frame 1,204)
      - Foreign - Canada - Association of Universities and Colleges of Canada Directory, 1964-1973 (Reel 106, Frame 1)
      - Foreign - Canada - The Atkinson Charitable Foundation, 1948-1973 (Reel 106, Frame 24)
      - Foreign - Canada - J. P. Brickell Foundation, 1970-1974 (Reel 106, Frame 92)
      - Foreign - Canada - The Canada Council, 1959-1974 (Reel 106, Frame 101)
      - Foreign - Canada - Foundation J. - Louis Levesque, 1970-1971 (Reel 106, Frame 157)
      - Foreign - Canada - The Richard Ivey Foundation, 1958-1974 (Reel 106, Frame 170)
      - Foreign - Canada - The Richard & Jean Ivey Foundation, 1971-1973 (Reel 106, Frame 182)
      - Foreign - Canada - Laidlaw Fuondation, 1963-1973 (Reel 106, Frame 186)
      - Foreign - Canada - The R. Samuel McLaughlin Foundation, 1970-1971 (Reel 106, Frame 206)
      - Foreign - Canada - Vancouver Foundation, 1961-1974 (Reel 106, Frame 213)
      - Foreign - Canada - The Winnipeg Foundation, 1956-1974 (Reel 106, Frame 230)
      - Foreign - Cameroon, 1972 (Reel 106, Frame 262)
      - Foreign - Chile, 1969 (Reel 106, Frame 267)
      - Foreign - Colombia - Fundacion Hernando Carvajal B., 1972-1975 (Reel 106, Frame 270)
      - Foreign - Denmark, 1970-1972 (Reel 106, Frame 282)
      - Foreign - Denmark - Landsindsamlingens Fond, 1970 (Reel 106, Frame 288)
      - Foreign - Denmark - Otto Monsteds Fond, 1970-1971 (Reel 106, Frame 291)
      - Foreign - Denmark - The Novo Foundation, 1970 (Reel 106, Frame 294)
      - Foreign - Dominican Republic, 1971-1975 (Reel 106, Frame 297)
      - Foreign - Ecuador, 1971-1975 (Reel 106, Frame 354)
      - Foreign - El Salvador, 1973 (Reel 106, Frame 371)
      - Foreign - England - The Animal Health Trust, 1970 (Reel 106, Frame 379)
      - Foreign - England - Charities Aid Fund, 1967-1971 (Reel 106, Frame 383)
      - Foreign - England - The Charity Commission, 1960-1974 (Reel 106, Frame 443)
      - Foreign - England - The Ciba Foundation, 1969-1974 (Reel 106, Frame 523)
      - Foreign - England - The Commonwealth Foundation, 1966-1974 (Reel 106, Frame 533)
      - Foreign - England - The Ditchley Foundation, 1966-1969 (Reel 106, Frame 590)
      - Foreign - England - Foundation for Management Education, 1970 (Reel 106, Frame 799)
      - Foreign - England - Calouste Gulbenkian Foundation - Lisbon, 1971-1973 (Reel 106, Frame 803)
      - Foreign - England - International Foundation Directory, 1973-1974 (Reel 106, Frame 808)
      - Foreign - England - Guy W. Keeling, 1948-1960 (Reel 106, Frame 833)
      - Foreign - England - The P. D. Leake Trust, 1970 (Reel 106, Frame 883)
      - Foreign - England - The Leverhulme Trust Fund, 1969-1973 (Reel 106, Frame 887)
      - Foreign - England - Nathan Committee, 1952-1963 (Reel 106, Frame 901)
      - Foreign - England - The Nuffield Foundation, 1957-1973 (Reel 106, Frame 923)
      - Foreign - England - The Pilgrim Trust, 1966-1971 (Reel 106, Frame 1,043)
      - Foreign - England - The Plunkett Foundation, 1970 (Reel 106, Frame 1,052)
      - Foreign - England - Political and Economic Planning, 1966-1969 (Reel 106, Frame 1,058)
      - Foreign - England - Ramsay Memorial Fellowships Trust, 1970-1974 (Reel 106, Frame 1,072)
      - Foreign - England - Reference Center on Charitable Trusts and Foundations, 1960-1961 (Reel 106, Frame 1,083)
      - Foreign - England - Joseph Rowntree Memorial Trust, 1961-1966 (Reel 106, Frame 1,117)